Privacy Policy
==============

General
-------

Speaker Deck LLC collects e-mail addresses of people who send us e-mail. We also collect information on what pages consumers access and information provided to us by consumers via surveys and deck uploads. Such information may contain personal data about you including your address, phone numbers, credit card numbers etc. We are not allowed to disclose such personal information without your written permission. However, certain information collected from you and about you is used within the context of providing the Service. The information we collect is not shared with or sold to others except under the certain circumstances and which your use of the Service is deemed to provide us a valid consent to disclose the following:

* In order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of [Speaker Deck’s terms of service](https://speakerdeck.com/tos), or as otherwise required by law.
* Speaker Deck LLC does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested or when we have your permission.
* We will transfer information about you if Speaker Deck or Speaker Deck LLC is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Speaker Deck LLC will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Speaker Deck web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

* * *

What we do with your information
--------------------------------

* When you register for Speaker Deck we ask for your email address, a username, and optionally your first and last name. You do not need a credit card to sign up.
* Speaker Deck LLC uses the information we collect for the following general purposes: products and services provision, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

* * *

Security
--------

The security of your personal information is important to us. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [\[email protected\]](https://speakerdeck.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

* * *

Disclosure
----------

Speaker Deck may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with court orders requiring us to do so or when your actions violate the [Terms of Service](https://speakerdeck.com/tos).

* * *

Data Storage
------------

Speaker Deck LLC owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the Speaker Deck application however we make no claim to the rights of your data.

* * *

Cookies
-------

A cookie is a small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Speaker Deck uses cookies to record current session information, our cookies generally last two weeks. You are required to log-in to your Speaker Deck account after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing the content of your account.

* * *

Changes to this Privacy Policy
------------------------------

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
